[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What are the two classes of encryption algorithms?",
    "choices": [
      "open",
      "symmetric",
      "asymmetric",
      "classic",
      "advanced"
    ],
    "answer": [1, 2],
    "type": "multiple-choice-v2",
    "category": "Cloud Security"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What term is used to describe the phenomenon of more VMs than can be managed effectively?",
    "choices": [
      "VM Scaling",
      "VM Exhaustion",
      "VM Escape",
      "VM Sprawl"
    ],
    "answer": 3,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Cloud Security"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which cloud security domain covers the challenges of delivering, measuring, and communicating compliances when organizations migrate from traditional data centers to the cloud?",
    "choices": [
      "Infrastructure Security",
      "Management Plane and Business Continuity",
      "Information Governance",
      "Compliance and Audit Management"
    ],
    "answer": 3,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Cloud Security"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "A company is deploying a product ordering system on a public cloud. The company IT specialist is working on security measures to protect the cloud resources. What are two possible negative impacts that should be considered when deploying a virtual firewall and an IPS appliance?",
    "choices": [
      "compatibility with VM operating systems",
      "routing issues associated with virtual security appliances",
      "traffic bottleneck",
      "possible VM escape attacks",
      "processor overloading"
    ],
    "answer": [2, 4],
    "type": "multiple-choice-v2",
    "category": "Cloud Security"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What should be deployed to protect traffic confidentiality between a public cloud and a private cloud?",
    "choices": [
      "proxy device",
      "IPS",
      "VPN",
      "firewall"
    ],
    "answer": 2,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Cloud Security"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "In which type of environment would a developer run software to verify that required security settings are met prior to production deployment?",
    "choices": [
      "sandbox environment",
      "development environment",
      "production environment",
      "staging environment"
    ],
    "answer": 3,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Cloud Security"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Which state of data refers to data moving between the CPU and the hard drive of a server?",
    "choices": [
      "data in storage",
      "data in process",
      "data in transit",
      "data at rest"
    ],
    "answer": 2,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Cloud Security"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Which technology is used to verify the integrity of files to ensure they were not modified in transit?",
    "choices": [
      "asymmetric encryption",
      "checksum",
      "secure cookies",
      "normalization"
    ],
    "answer": 1,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Cloud Security"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Which threat type describes the case when cloud computing resources are set up incorrectly?",
    "choices": [
      "inside threat",
      "cloud misconfiguration",
      "data breaches",
      "poor cloud security architecture strategy"
    ],
    "answer": 1,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Cloud Security"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What term is used to refer to readable data in the context of the data encryption process?",
    "choices": [
      "ciphertext",
      "cleantext",
      "opentext",
      "plaintext"
    ],
    "answer": 3,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Cloud Security"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Which key component of virtualization allows for running multiple independent operating systems on one physical computing system?",
    "choices": [
      "VDI",
      "hypervisor",
      "VM",
      "container"
    ],
    "answer": 1,
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "category": "Cloud Security"
  }
]